National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name!
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Come here!
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
You need deliverance, she needs deliverance.
You have the spirit of lizard.
I can smell it.
In Jesus' name.
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Wow, can you see?
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Who are you?
I am the king of Asia.
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
No!
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
You are free!
National Healing Campaign In Singapore
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Thank You, Jesus!
My name is Margaret Tansinwah. I am 39 years old.
I am from Singapore.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, he prophesied that I had an evil spirit of lizard.
It was very true because both I and my daughter had evil spirits.
I wanted to kill my daughter.
The spirit of lizard in me has gone out, and I am set free.
My daughter has also been set free.
Now that you have been set free and delivered, what is your promise to God?
My promise is to serve the Lord.
I am telling what I know
About Jesus of Nazareth.
My name is Margaret Tansinwah. I am 39 years old.
I am a Singaporean.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me,
he prophesied that there was a spirit of lizard in me and in my daughter.
It was very true.
The evil spirit in me would ask me to harm my daughter;
I would get angry, and I would want to kill her.
After the man of God, Prophet T.B.Joshua, prayed for me,
I no longer need to take all this medicine to go to bed.
I am set free.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
All of these are very expensive drugs.
They are very wanted by drug addicts.
They are all sleeping pills and are not sold over the counter.
Do you mean that you used to take these before your deliverance?
Yes, you can see a lot of medicines - nasal drips, against bronchitis, sleeping pills.
My daughter had to have nasal drops since she was 3 years old.
Can you tell us - what happened to you yesterday when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you?
I was set free.
We no longer need this medicine.
I slept like a baby.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
We are set free and I love my daughter.
Madam, how do you feel today ?
I feel great; I woke up without any headaches.
Amen, put your hands together for Jesus.
Praise the Lord!
I confirm that the evil spirit in me is gone because I no longer hear any voices.
You mean, you are free, in Jesus' name.
Yes, I am free, in Jesus' name.
Hallelujah! Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
Thank you very much.
God bless you, in Jesus' name.
RV: Mel Flowers 06/04/2019
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, service and testimonies from the SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV, changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.